{
    "subject": "Debra_McGrath",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Colin_Mochrie",
    "human_readable": "Debra McGrath is married to Colin Mochrie.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9107825756072998,
            "question": "To whom is Colin Mochrie married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9086622595787048,
            "question": "Who is married to Colin Mochrie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9032288789749146,
            "question": "Are Debra McGrath and Colin Mochrie in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.902961015701294,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the relationship between Debra McGrath and Colin Mochrie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9008933305740356,
            "question": "Is Debra McGrath married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8502359390258789,
            "question": "Is Colin Mochrie married to someone famous?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7301209568977356,
            "question": "What is the name of Colin Mochrie's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7132908701896667,
            "question": "What is the name of Colin Mochrie's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6769663691520691,
            "question": "Who shares a marital relationship with Colin Mochrie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.667267382144928,
            "question": "Who is Debra McGrath?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Debra McGrath is married to Colin Mochrie.",
            "html": "yago_10411_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who shares a marital relationship with Colin Mochrie?",
            "html": "yago_10411_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Colin Mochrie's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_10411_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Colin Mochrie's wife?",
            "html": "yago_10411_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10411_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10411_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10411_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10411_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10411_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10411_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10411_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10411_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10411_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10411_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the context information, I found that the triple \"Debra McGrath is married to Colin Mochrie\" is supported by several documents:\n\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_10411/re-ranker-msmarco/30.txt states that Debra McGrath and Colin Mochrie have been married for 35 years.\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_10411/re-ranker-msmarco/2.txt confirms their marriage in 1989.\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_10411/re-ranker-msmarco/107.txt states that Colin Mochrie married Debra McGrath in 1989.\n\nTherefore, the final answer is:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple pieces of information confirming that Debra McGrath and Colin Mochrie are indeed married. For example, the document at `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_10411/re-ranker-msmarco/104.txt` states \"Colin Mochrie is currently married to Debra McGrath,\" and another document indicates they have been married for 35 years."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}